now obviously uh tonight I need to talk
about what's going on in South Carolina
uh I want to say something for the
record now last Saturday a white cop in
South Carolina killed a black man named
Walter Scott officer Michael slagger
stopped Scott for a busted tail light
not a violent crime and somehow Scott
wound up dead the police immediately
went on the record saying that Scott had
gained control of the officer taser and
that's why the officer shot him now
later slagger said through his attorney
that he felt threatened and fired his
weapon and so for the record this crazy
black thug was attacking him and he did
what he had to do but also for the
record this time we actually have the
record there's a cell phone video of the
shooting Which Scott is trying to run
away and this cop shoots him in the back
five times killing
him now for the actual record it appears
that officer slager immediately began
the cover up of Walter Scott's death he
handcuffed Scott as he lay bleeding on
the ground then he picked up what looks
like an awful lot like that taser and
laid it next to Scott's dying body
presumably didn't make it look like
Scott was armed during the altercation
so end of story right another black man
shot in the back by a cup I mean it's as
American as an apple pie filled with
baseballs cooked by bald eagle with the
head of guy
Fier all right yesterday after the video
emerged officer Michael slager was
charged with murder and that's the great
news thank
you by the way that's how low the bar is
right now on great
news right I mean the fact that a cop
who coldly murdered someone on camera
even faces the remote possibility of
justice is giving me the warm
fuzzies and for the record all this good
news does is make me think about how
many of these murders aren't caught on
camera here let me show you a video of
another violent altercation between
citizens and police now this cop is
great okay he's got the one guy pinned
and then this other guy comes up you've
got these drunk Jack wads threatening
him and he's using look at that non he's
wrestling them look when is the gun
going to come out when is the gun gonna
look now he's detaining two crazy Bros
who are wilding out oh this is going to
turn tragic any
second wait that's
it these two white guys jumped a police
officer and they wind up in a three-way
sand tickle
fight and the brother in South Carolina
was running from the cop and he's not
alive
today I said it once before I'll stop
talking about this when it stops
happening for the record we'll be right
back hey America follow the nightly show
with Larry Wilmore on Twitter but don't
follow me home I want followers but I
don't want followers that's stalking